Joseph (Joe) McHugh, Jr. Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
Joseph (Joe) McHugh, Jr. Collection
1968 - 2012
1970 - 1973
NPkMC-225-022
2 Linear Feet
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
Marist College
Joseph McHugh was both a student and crew coach at Marist College. His collection covers Marist men’s crew team history as well as some of his own personal history.
Collection Overview
This collection contains newspaper and magazine clippings, pamphlets, schedules, photos, negatives, a postcard, 2 maps, 3 tags, a piece of correspondence, 2 sports cards, a poster, and a scrapbook.
Joseph McHugh was both a student and crew coach at Marist College. His collection covers Marist men’s crew team history as well as some of his own personal history. While the collection spans from 1969 to 2012, the majority of materials originate from the period of 1970 to 1973. There are no materials covering the period of 1977-2000 or 2002-2011.
Acquisitions Informantion
The Collection was donated to Marist College by Joseph McHugh in 2013.
Restrictions to Access
There are no restrictions on this collection
The collection is arranged into five subseries: 1) Clippings, 2) Graphic Materials, 3) Objects, 4) Pamphlets and Schedules, and 5) Personal Materials, has two subseries, 5.1) Marist College and 5.2) Family History.
- 1. Clippings, 1968 - 1976; 1; Folders: 1 - 14 Box: 1
  - Child's Cup Regatta, 1971, undated (Folder 1, Box 1)
  - Cypress Garden Regatta, undated (Folder 2, Box 1)
  - Dad Vail Regatta, 1975-1976, undated (Folder 3, Box 1)
  - Head-of-the-Charles Regatta, 1970, undated (Folder 4, Box 1)
  - High School Crew Teams, 1968, undated (Folder 5, Box 1)
  - Marist Crew Team, 1970-1973,1976 (Folder 6, Box 1)
  - Marist Crew Team, undated (Folder 7, Box 1)
  - Marist Crew Team Rivals, 1970, undated (Folder 8, Box 1)
  - National Intercollegiate Rowing, undated (Folder 9, Box 1)
  - President's Cup Regatta, 1969-1974, undated (Folder 10, Box 1)
  - Rusty Callow Regatta, undated (Folder 11, Box 1)
  - Spring Fever Regatta, 1972 (Folder 12, Box 1)
  - Trinity Regatta, 1972 (Folder 13, Box 1)
  - Women's Crew at Marist, 1974, 1976, undated (Folder 14, Box 1)
- 2. Graphic Materials, 2; Folders: 15 - 17 Box: 1
  - Detroit Boat Club Regatta, 1976 (Folder 15, Box 1)
  - Head of the Charles Regatta, undated (Folder 16, Box 1)
  - Maps of the Poughkeepsie Area, undated (Folder 17, Box 1)
- 3. Objects, 1973 - 1976; 3; Folders: 18 - 20 Box: 1
  - Head-of-the-Charles Regatta Tags, undated (Folder 18, Box 1)
  - Marist Crew Team Scrapbook, 1973-1976, undated (Folder 19, Box 1)
  - Syracuse Regatta Tag, 1974 (Folder 20, Box 1)
- 4. Pamphlets and Schedules, 1971 - 1976; 4; Folders: 21 - 30 Box: 1
  - Crew Regatta - Pittsfield, Ma, 1976 (Folder 21, Box 1)
  - Dad Vail Rowing Regatta, 1970-1972 (Folder 22, Box 1)
  - Head-of-the-Charles Regatta, 1970-1972 (Folder 23, Box 1)
  - Junior Rowing Championship, 1971 (Folder 24, Box 1)
  - Marist College Crew Team, 1972, 1974, undated (Folder 25, Box 1)
  - National Association of Amateur Oarsmen, 1976 (Folder 26, Box 1)
  - National Intercollegiate Rowing Championships, 1973-1974 (Folder 27, Box 1)
  - President's Cup Regatta, 1976, undated (Folder 28, Box 1)
  - Trinity College Regatta, 1972 (Folder 29, Box 1)
  - Wesleyan University Regattas, 1971-1972 (Folder 30, Box 1)
- 5. Personal Materials, 1970 - 2012; 5; Folders: 1 - 7 Box: 2
  - Subseries 5.1: Marist College, 1970 - 1972; 5.1; Folders: 1 - 4 Box: 2
    - Clippings, undated (Folder 1, Box 2)
    - Correspondence, 1970 (Folder 2, Box 2)
    - Pamphlet, undated (Folder 3, Box 2)
    - River Day Poster, 1972 (Folder 4, Box 2)
  - Subseries 5.2: Family History, 2001 - 2012; 5.2; Folders: 5 - 7 Box: 2
    - Sports Cards, 2001, 2012 (Folder 5, Box 2)
    - Media Images, 2002, undated (Folder 6, Box 2)
    - Family Photos, undated (Folder 7, Box 2)